<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Pages on Nahshon Wiltshire&#39;s Blog</title>
        <link>https://github.com/NahshonWiltshireMIU/gettoknownahshon.github.io/page/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Pages on Nahshon Wiltshire&#39;s Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://github.com/NahshonWiltshireMIU/gettoknownahshon.github.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Fun Fact</title>
        <link>https://github.com/NahshonWiltshireMIU/gettoknownahshon.github.io/page/facts/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://github.com/NahshonWiltshireMIU/gettoknownahshon.github.io/page/facts/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My interest in computers and technology began at a very early stage in my life. I would have begun tinkering with a variety of devices, including FM radios, cell phones and computer desktops. Of course at times I would often worsen the issue before actually getting it resolved. Later in life I was introduced to the microsoft suite and in particular microsoft excel and the various formulas enhanced with the drag and drop capabilities which would copy the formula and update referenced fields based on pattens observed. Working with excel led me to realize that work can be lessened by using general instructions. In secondary school, I was introduced to a scripting language called pascal, it was then I truly saw the concept behind programming. I would have now known that at the end of the day, software is basically bundling code for solving a particular problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would have went on to college to pursue a degree in Computer Science at the Dominica State College, there I learnt object oriented programming, networking, database management and web design. From then on, my vision was clear I worked towards becoming better in the field of technology.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
